pageflakes.com 2006-12-09

# Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy_**

 **Registration**

·         You can use Pageflakes without registering.

·         If you want Pageflakes to remember your settings permanently or if you want to access your personal page from more than one PC you need to register with your email address and a password. In addition this will also protect your account from unauthorized access.

·         When you register we’ll send you a welcome email.

·         We may send you important service announcements on rare occasions. You can unsubscribe from these announcements at any time by sending an email to _unsubscribe@pageflakes.com_.

·         We will never sell or rent your email address.

 **Your settings**

·         You may choose to submit additional information in order to personalize your page (such as a ZIP code to customize your weather forecast).

·         Non-personally identifiable data: When you use an application which has been developed by a third party and has been integrated into the Pageflakes site (or an application that interacts with applications from other sites) it can be necessary to transmit data that you have entered at Pageflakes to the provider of that application. For example, if you enter your ZIP code in order to get local weather information, Pageflakes will transmit your ZIP code to a weather information site to get your weather forecast.

·         Personally identifiable data: You may choose to use third-party applications which require entering additional information or signing in to an existing user account at the application provider. For example, if you choose to access your email from Pageflakes, you need to enter the email host, address and password, which will subsequently be used to receive emails from your email service.

·         If information is transmitted to a third-party application, only information that is required to use the respective application properly will be transmitted.

 **Other data:**

·         Cookies: Cookies are small files that allow web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site. Cookies are required to use Pageflakes.

·         IP address: Your IP address may be used to address problems with our server or administer our site or to gather broad demographic information about our users.

·         Log information: When you use Pageflakes, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

·         Aggregated information: We may share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users.

 **Contextual Advertising**

We may use software that processes the content displayed on your personalized page to deliver relevant ads to you. This will be done using a completely automated process, no human will read the content of your page.

 **Crawlers**

Your personalized page and the information that you enter at Pageflakes cannot be crawled by search engines like Google.

 **Tell-A-Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We may store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at _privacy@pageflakes.com_ to request that we remove this information from our database.

 **Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law or court order.

 **Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement at _www.pageflakes.com/privacy.html_. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on our home page.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at _privacy@pageflakes.com_.
